# **Hadi Gunawan**

hadigunawan987@gmail.com | +6285781722743 | South Tangerang, Banten 15224 | linkedin.com/in/hadi-gunawan-875889199/ | Portfolio

#### **SUMMARY**

Hello, my name is Hadi Gunawan and I am a fresh graduate from the University of Pamulang majoring in Informatics Engineering, I have work experience for approximately 2 years. Tech-savvy, I have an enthusiasm to have a career in the data field for instance: Data Analyst, Data Scientist, etc, but do not rule out opportunities in other fields. Eager to learn and adapt to a new technology tool or method used.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Retention and Winback, Myrepublic ID

Aug 2018 - July 2020

- Make outbound calls to customers who have a disconnected status of subscription in order to minimize the occurrence of churn, using customer data from CRM (customer and target oriented)
- **Escalated reports** related to customer problems and rewards to customers. Using google sheets, CRM and tools for instance: Zendesk, internal CRM
- Communicate with other co-workers with same or in another division to achieve target goals

## Data Entry Assistant Intern, BP2T South Tangerang

Jan 2016 - Feb 2016

- Entry data into Microsoft Excel
- Organizing a pysical data into the warehouse and maintaining them

#### LICENSE AND CERTIFICATIONS

### SQL Fundamentals Track (DataCamp)

Learning and practicing about Structured Query Language (SQL), in this course I learning from basic to intermediate, window function, correlated queries, nested queries, Common Table Expressions (CTE), built-in PostgreSQL functions and many more

# Python Fundamentals Track (DataCamp)

Learning and practicing about python from basic (focused on data analysis), learn some packages such as NumPy, matplotlib and Pandas

### Tableau Fundamentals Track (DataCamp)

Learning and practicing about data preparation, identification, data visualization, insight, dashboard, story using tableau.

#### And many more..

#### **SKILLS**

**Hard Skills and Tools:** Visual Studio Code, Excel, Word, PowerPoint, SQL, Tableau, Power Bi, Google Sheets, Google Data Studio, HTML, CSS, Github, MySQL, Adobe Photoshop, (Novice: SQL Server, PHP, Python, Flutter, AWS)

Soft Skills: Communication, Critical Thinking, Teamwork, Adaptability, Prosedural Thinking

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Informatic Engineering **University of Pamulang** 

Sept 2017 – Aug 2021 GPA: 3.46

**Relevant coursework:** Database, Algorithms and Programming, Data Communication, Statistics, Informatics Logic, Calculus, Basic Physics, Computer Programming, Data Structures, AI, DSS.